ecwpress.com 2019-05-01

# ECW Press | A Canadian Indie Book Publisher | Publishing Curiously Compelling Books Since 1974

_Last updated on September 4, 2018_

Welcome to the ECW PRESS (“ **ECW PRESS** ” or “ **we** ” or “ **us** ”) Privacy Policy. This online Privacy Policy tells you what information ECW PRESS collects at its websites accessed as: www.ECWpress.com. By accessing, browsing, subscribing to, or otherwise using the ECW PRESS website and accepting the terms and conditions for such ECW PRESS website, you agree that ECW PRESS may collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information as described in this policy. “Personal Information” means information about you, alone or in conjunction with other information, that may be used to identify you.

#### **PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

We reserve the right to modify, alter, or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this policy from time to time. The current version of this Privacy Policy will be posted on the ECW PRESS website at all times. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this Agreement. Your continued use of the ECW PRESS website following the posting of any changes means you agree to be bound by such changes.

#### **PURPOSES FOR COLLECTING YOUR INFORMATION**

We collect Personal Information from you to:

  * process your purchase orders for our products and services

  * provide you with other customer support and communication

  * better understand your preferences and provide you with newsletters and other tailored offers if you opt in to receive them

  * conduct analyses and evaluations to improve our ECW PRESS website, products, services, and marketing communications

We may also: (i) respond to your inquiries and provide you with information and communicate with you about products, listings, events, and services you request; and (ii) communicate relevant offers and targeted listings to you if you opt in to receive them.

By consenting to our collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information through your use of the ECW PRESS website (including any products and services available on the ECW PRESS website), you will allow us to fulfill the purposes for which we collect your Personal Information, as described above or communicated to you at the time of information collection.

#### **COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

ECW PRESS regards the privacy of all users as of utmost importance. We will take all **commercially reasonable** means necessary to protect any information you may give us. We only collect Personal Information that you provide or that is otherwise provided to us on your behalf (such as your name, address, phone number, email address, etc.). By providing your Personal Information to us, you implicitly agree that we may collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Unless we advise otherwise, your information will only be used for the purposes for which it was provided or to contact you. We will limit the information we collect to what we need for those purposes.

####  **DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  

We do not disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your consent unless required or permitted by applicable law. We will not rent, sell, loan, or otherwise market your Personal Information to any third party. There are some situations in which we may disclose your Personal Information without your consent. For example:

  * when we are required or authorized by law to do so, for example if a court issues a subpoena

  * when the services we are providing to you require us to give your information to a third party your consent will be implied, unless you tell us otherwise

  * when we believe we need to disclose information to protect our rights, or the rights of others, property, or to enforce this Privacy Policy or the terms and conditions of the ECW PRESS website, including where it is necessary to establish or collect amounts owed to us

  * if the information is public record information specified by regulation and the disclosure is directly related to the purposes for which it was recorded on the public record

We may transfer your personal information to service providers who are performing services on our behalf. These service providers will be obligated to treat your personal information in accordance with the requirements of this Privacy Policy.

Occasionally, we may use service providers located outside of Canada to process and/or store Personal Information for us. Please note that Personal Information in the custody of these service providers may be subject to access by the law enforcement authorities of those jurisdictions in which the service providers are located. Our Privacy Officer, whose contact information is provided below, can provide further information about our policies and practices regarding service providers located outside of Canada and further information about how these service providers collect, use, disclose, or store personal information on our behalf.

In the event that our company undergoes a fundamental change such as a sale of assets, or a merger with another company or enterprise, it may be necessary for us to disclose your Personal Information to the prospective counterparties to the transaction and their professional advisors. No such disclosure will occur unless these entities have executed confidentiality agreements in respect of your Personal Information and limit their use of it to the purposes necessary for completing the transaction and the operation of the business after the transaction is complete.

####  **CONSENT**  

When you provide us with your Personal Information, you agree that you are providing us your implied consent to collect and use your Personal Information to fulfill the requested order, service, or information. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information at any time. However, please note that, for certain services, if you withdraw your consent, we may no longer be able to provide the service to you.

Additionally, if you opt in to receive promotional emails, every email will contain an “unsubscribe” link that you can click to withdraw your consent and remove your email address from further promotional messages.

#### **ACCURACY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

It is important that the information you provide us is accurate and updated. You have a right to challenge the accuracy and completeness of your Personal Information and to have it amended, as appropriate. You also have a right to request access to your Personal Information and receive an accounting of how that information has been used and disclosed, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. For example, if the requested information would reveal Personal Information about another individual, your access may be limited or denied. If your request for access is denied, we will notify you in writing and explain why.

To request access or to amend your Personal Information, please contact our Privacy Officer at the address below.

#### **RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You may contact our Privacy Officer to ask us to remove your Personal Information from our records, electronic or otherwise. However, we will need to maintain certain Personal Information about you as long as reasonably necessary for us to complete our dealings with you, or as may be required by law. For example, we will maintain Personal Information about any purchases you may make on the ECW PRESS website for purposes such as warranty and product information.

####  **COOKIES**  

Like most other organizations, we may monitor traffic patterns, site usage, and related site information. ECW PRESS website servers will automatically collect IP addresses, and we may use a browser feature called a “cookie”. A cookie is a small file placed on your hard drive that enables us to optimize your visit to the ECW PRESS Website and to record session information, such as items added to your shopping cart. You can usually configure your internet browser to reject cookies. However, if you do so, you might not be able to access certain pages or use important functions on the ECW PRESS website.

ECW PRESS uses cookies for a variety of purposes that include site navigation, shopping cart, to remember personal preferences, to remember pages and products of interest. Some cookies are automatically deleted at the end of the session and others persist until you delete them using your browser settings.

ECW PRESS uses Google Analytics to collect information on how our website is used with the goal of improving the user experience. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect information and may also report on use of other websites, apps, and online resources. If you do not wish to allow Google Analytics to collect such information, you can download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on").

#### **LINKS TO PARTNERING ORGANIZATIONS**

ECW PRESS works with a number of partners who have their own privacy policies. ECW PRESS is not responsible for the privacy policies of partnering organizations; interested parties should review the privacy policies of those sites. If you have subscribed to a product, service, or promotional program, such as a newsletter, or are participating in a contest, promotion, or event that is offered by a third party together with ECW PRESS or under an ECW PRESS brand, you may also have to provide your consent or withdraw your consent with that third party separately. For further information on the manner in which our partnering organizations process your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer at the address below.

####  **LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES**  

We may provide links to other websites that are not affiliated with us. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies, or how they treat information about their users, and we advise you to check their privacy policies before providing any Personal Information to them.

####  **PRIVACY OFFICER CONTACT INFORMATION**  

If you have any questions or complaints about our privacy practices, including accessing or amending your Personal Information, please feel free to contact our Privacy Officer:

ECW PRESS Privacy Officer   
665 Gerrard Street East   
Toronto ON M4M 1Y2   
Canada

Email the ECW PRESS Privacy Officer at [this address](mailto:info@ecwpress.com "info@ecwpress.com").
